<Treatment>
    <Name>
        Medication
    </Name>
    <Description>
        __*Overactive Bladder Treatment*__ is designed to help you manage your overactive bladder and improve your qulity of life. 
        Press the start button and let's get started.
    </Description>
    <CONTENT>
        # What is Overactive Bladder (OAB)?

        Overactive bladder (OAB) is the name for a group of urinary symptoms. It is not a disease. The most common symptom is a sudden, uncontrolled need or urge to urinate. Some people will leak urine when they feel this urge. Another symptom is the need to pass urine many times during the day and night. OAB is basically the feeling that you’ve “gotta’ go” to the bathroom urgently and too much.

        ## Key Statistics

        As many as 30 percent of men and 40 percent of women in the United States live with OAB symptoms. Many people living with OAB don't ask for help. They may feel embarrassed. Many people either don't know how to talk with their health care provider about their symptoms, or they think there aren't treatments that can help.

        The truth is there are many treatments that can help. Asking your health care provider about it is the first step.


        ## How OAB Can Affect Your Life
        OAB can get in the way of your work, social life, exercise and sleep. Without treatment, OAB symptoms can make it hard to get through the day without many trips to the bathroom. You may not want to go out with friends or go far from home because you're afraid of being far from a bathroom. This makes many people feel lonely and isolated.

        OAB may affect relationships with friends and family. It can disrupt your sleep and sex-life. Too little sleep will leave anyone tired and depressed. In addition, if you leak urine, you may develop skin problems or infections.

        You don't have to let OAB rule your life. OAB can be controlled. If you think you have OAB, see your health care provider.

        ![](https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/articles/image_article_collections/anatomy_pages/heart_illustration.jpg?resize=646px:*&output-quality=100)

        ## The Truth About OAB

        - OAB is not a normal part of getting older.
        - OAB is not just part of being a woman.
        - OAB is not just an issue with the prostate.
        - OAB is not caused by something you did.
        - Surgery is not the only treatment for OAB.
        - There are treatments to help people manage OAB symptoms.
        - There are treatments to help even minor OAB symptoms.

        If you are bothered by OAB symptoms, then you should ask for treatment!

        ### this is just a heading level 3
        hello 

        #### and this is four

        #“Tom and Jerry” – a favorite for decades
        Tom and Jerry is a hilarious American Television series that has been running since the 1940s. It has been ranked, as one of the best cartoon series of all time and is one of the longest running cartoon series. Each episode consists of two short films about a cat named Tom and a mouse named Jerry, who constantly argue and fight. Tom and Jerry is based around slapstick comedy, which “…is the recourse to humor involving exaggerated physical activity, which exceeds the boundaries of common sense.”

        

        Tom, is a grey cat, who usually lives a pampered life, and takes pleasure in tormenting a mouse named Jerry. Jerry, is a small, brown mouse, who lives in the same house as Tom. Each episode usually revolves around Tom and Jerry quarreling and chasing each other around. Most episodes end in Jerry being the triumphant one out of the two. Although Tom constantly chases Jerry he hardly ever tries to eat him. Although they fight and argue a lot, at the end of some episodes, Tom and Jerry set aside their differences and act like friends. In fact, if either Tom or Jerry is put in grave danger, the other is willing to do his best to help and try save the other.

        ##The series’ recurring characters
        Spike and Tyke

        Tom and Jerry has some reoccurring characters throughout the series which include Spike and Tike, Butch, Toodles Galore, and Nibbles. Spike is a vicious and sometimes unintelligent dog. Although at times he lets his temper get the best of him, he always has a soft spot for his son, Tike. Tike is Spike’s young, innocent, sweet, and lovable son. In the episodes Spike and Tike are seen in throughout the series, Spike constantly chases around Tom.
        

        If anything ever happens to Spike or Tike, Spike immediately blames Tom no matter what the circumstance and begins to chase him. Butch is a black cat, who is acquainted with Tom. Most often, Butch and Tom are seen fighting over a lady cat named Toodles Galore. The one thing Tom and Butch do have in common, however, is that they both want to catch Jerry. Nibbles is Jerry’s young and care-free nephew. Nibbles is less aware of his surroundings than Jerry is, which sometimes gets him into trouble. Nibbles, is also part of the mousketeers along with Jerry.

        

        ## Less talk and more slapstick
        Since it is a slapstick comedy, not much talking goes on throughout the Tom and Jerry series. Although Tom and Jerry themselves only talk a little, other reoccurring characters such as Butch and Spike, have quite a few lines in their episodes. When Tom and Jerry do talk, Tom usually has the most lines. Tom’s lines usually consist of him singing to his “love” Toodles Galore, in an attempt to gain her affection.

        Tom and Jerry was created by William Hanna and Joseph Barbera in 1940. Since then, Tom and Jerry has been directed and produced by many different people and companies. These include William Hanna and Joseph Barbera from 1940-1958, Gene Deitch from 1961-1962, Chuck Jones 1963-1967, William Hanna and Joseph Barbera again for a second time from 1975–1977, Ted Turner in 1986, William Hanna and Joseph Barbera for a third time from 1990–1994 and the Warner Bros. from 2006-2008.
    </CONTENT>
    <SubSections>
        <Section>
            <Name>
                OAB Section 1
            </Name>
            <Description>
        __*Overactive Bladder Treatment*__ is designed to help you manage your overactive bladder and improve your qulity of life. 
        Press the start button and let's get started.
            </Description>
            <CONTENT>
               # What is Overactive Bladder (OAB)?

        Overactive bladder (OAB) is the name for a group of urinary symptoms. It is not a disease. The most common symptom is a sudden, uncontrolled need or urge to urinate. Some people will leak urine when they feel this urge. Another symptom is the need to pass urine many times during the day and night. OAB is basically the feeling that you’ve “gotta’ go” to the bathroom urgently and too much.

        ## Key Statistics

        As many as 30 percent of men and 40 percent of women in the United States live with OAB symptoms. Many people living with OAB don't ask for help. They may feel embarrassed. Many people either don't know how to talk with their health care provider about their symptoms, or they think there aren't treatments that can help.

        The truth is there are many treatments that can help. Asking your health care provider about it is the first step.


        ## How OAB Can Affect Your Life
        OAB can get in the way of your work, social life, exercise and sleep. Without treatment, OAB symptoms can make it hard to get through the day without many trips to the bathroom. You may not want to go out with friends or go far from home because you're afraid of being far from a bathroom. This makes many people feel lonely and isolated.

        OAB may affect relationships with friends and family. It can disrupt your sleep and sex-life. Too little sleep will leave anyone tired and depressed. In addition, if you leak urine, you may develop skin problems or infections.

        You don't have to let OAB rule your life. OAB can be controlled. If you think you have OAB, see your health care provider.
            </CONTENT>
        </Section>
        <Section>
            <Name>
                OAB Section 2
            </Name>
            <Description>
                __*OAB Section 1 Desciption*__ 
            </Description>
            <CONTENT>
                # OAB Section 2 Heading Level 1 
                ## OAB Section 2 Heading Level 2 
                ## OAB Section 2 Heading Level 2 
                #### OAB Section 2 Heading Level 4
                ### OAB Section 2 Heading Level 3
            </CONTENT>
            <SubSections>
                <Section>
                    <Name>
                        OAB Section 2.1
                    </Name>
                    <Description>
                        __*OAB Section 2.1 Desciption*__ 
                    </Description>
                    <CONTENT>
                        # OAB Section 2.1 Heading Level 1 
                        ## OAB Section 2.1 Heading Level 2 
                        ## OAB Section 2.1 Heading Level 2 
                        #### OAB Section 2.1 Heading Level 4
                        ### OAB Section 2.1 Heading Level 3
                    </CONTENT>
                </Section>
            <SubSections>
        </Section>
    </SubSections>
</Treatment>



